checkmarx.com 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy

When you use our website, you consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure and other uses of your data as described in this Privacy Policy.

**What type of data we collect?**

When you access our website, we collect your IP address and information regarding your general location. We also use various technological tracking tools such as cookies which are used to store content information and preferences relating to your interactions with our website.

We also collect analytics data about the use of our website. This may include data related to website visits, page views, site interactions, browser type, display settings, operating system, device type, session start/stop time, referral URL, time zone, and network connection type. We may merge data collected through these tracking technologies and data we may obtain from other sources and, as a result, such data may become personal data.

We may receive your personal information when you communicate with us. For example, when you send us an email or contact us through the forms on our website, we will collect the information you provide to us. This information may include your email address, your telephone number, information about your company and your position, your country, and any other information submitted by you.

Our websites may include social media features. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie so that the social media feature works properly. Social media features are governed by the privacy policies of the website providing the feature.

We may receive personal data from our business partners. We may combine information collected about you with information from third party sources.

**How do we use the data we collect?**

We will use your data to operate our website, to communicate with you, to keep you informed of the latest updates to our website, products and services, and provide you with offers.

We may use your personal data for our internal marketing and promotional purposes. For example, by subscribing to our newsletter you will receive announcements from us. You may choose not to receive our promotional or marketing emails (all or any part thereof) by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the emails that you receive from us. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our communications, we may continue to send you product/service-related updates and notifications, or reply to your queries and feedback you provide us.

If you do not want us to use your personal data for marketing purposes, you may opt-out by sending an email request to [unsubscribe@checkmarx.com](mailto:unsubscribe@checkmarx.com). Please note that even if you opt-out, we may still use your data for non-marketing purposes (for example to fulfill your requests, communicate with you and respond to your inquiries, etc.).

From time to time, we may conduct surveys or test features, and analyze the data we have to develop, evaluate and improve these features, in order to better understand our customers and to improve our website, products and services.

We may use your personal data when we believe it’s necessary in order to take precautions against liabilities, investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, investigate and protect ourselves from fraud, protect the security or integrity of our services and protect the rights and property of Checkmarx, its users and/or partners. We may use your personal data in order to enforce our policies, including but not limited to our website Terms of Use. We may also use your personal data to investigate violations, and as required by law, regulation or other governmental authority, or to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

**With whom do we share your personal data?**

We share your information with companies in our group, as well as employees and contractors, in order to operate the website, to communicate with you, and to offer and provide our products and services to you.

We share your information with our third party service providers, such as web hosting providers, storage, customer management, analytics, survey and email service providers. These third parties may have access to your personal data so that they may provide these services on our behalf but they are not permitted by us to use your personal data for any other purpose.

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any data about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect our or a third party’s property and rights, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal data in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including meeting national security or law enforcement requirements.

We may share your data if we enter into a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or sale of some or all of our assets. Any party that acquires our assets as part of such a transaction may continue to use your data in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Transfer of data outside the EEA**

Please note that some data recipients may be located outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). In such cases, we will transfer your data only to such countries as approved by the European Commission as providing adequate level of data protection, or we will enter into legal agreements ensuring an adequate level of data protection in accordance with applicable law. By providing us your personal data, you hereby consent to such transfers of data outside the EEA.

**How we protect your information**

We have implemented administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of your data. We limit access of your information to those employees, subcontractors and service providers who require access to the data to discharge their duties to us.

While we seek to protect your information to ensure that it is kept confidential, we cannot absolutely guarantee its security. You should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet. While we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of your personal data or other content you transmit while using the website, and you do so at your own risk.

**Retention**

We will retain your personal data for as long as necessary to provide our website, products and services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing client personal data, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations.

**User rights**

You may request to:

  * Receive confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning you is being processed, and access your stored personal data, together with supplementary information.
  * Receive a copy of personal data you directly volunteer to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.
  * Request rectification of your personal data that is in our control.
  * Request erasure of your personal data.
  * Object to the processing of personal data by us.
  * Request to restrict processing of your personal data by us.
  * Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

However, please note that these rights are not absolute, and may also be subject to our own legitimate interests and regulatory requirements.

**How to contact us?**

If you wish to exercise any of the aforementioned rights, or to receive more information, please contact us using the contact details set out in the “Contact Us” portion of our website: <https://www.checkmarx.com/contact-us>.

**Updates to this Policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to changes from time to time, in our sole discretion. The most current version will always be posted on our website. Your continued use of the website or our services shall be deemed to be your consent to such changes.

Last updated: May 24, 2018
